You can open the project file by clicking on the corresponding option on the main menu, search for the file address, select it, and then click open to open the file.
After opening the project file, you can see that virtual models and costumes have appeared in the 3D and 2D windows at the same time.
Or you can drag the file from the library window to the 3D window to open it.
After opening the project file, you can choose to load the type and target.
If you choose to open it, the project file will be opened directly, and the original project file will not be stored in the 3D window.
If you choose to add, the new project file will be added to the working area.
When adding a file, you can set the moving option value.
Set the number of objects.
After entering the value of the x-axis, click the confirm button to add a file.
You can see that the new file will be added to the working area.
You can save the saved project files by clicking on the main menu to save, or you can do another layer according to the need.
Select the root path and enter the file name, then click save.
When you have a new object in the working area, you can select the file to create a new one.
In the new project file, only the virtual model file will be saved.
If you need to delete the virtual model, you can select virtual model and select save.
You can delete it by clicking Delete after selecting the virtual model.
You can open the clothing file by clicking the corresponding option in the menu.
Select the clothing file you need to open and click Open.
After opening the clothing file, you can see the clothing in the 3D and 2D windows at the same time.
When you upload the clothing file in the window where the mouse is selected, you can view the three-dimensional image.
Click and drag the clothing file to the 3D window to open the clothing file.
Select Open and click Confirm.
A new clothing file will appear in the 3D and 2D windows.
When you open the clothing file, click Add in the category and select Add.
You can add other clothing files to the environment.
You can set the moving properties according to your needs.
Click Save.
In the main menu, select the corresponding option to save the clothing file separately.
Select Save path, enter the name and click Save.
Click the corresponding option in the main menu to open the virtual model.
After selecting the virtual model file, click Open.
You can see the virtual model in the 3D window and the clothing in the 2D window appear at the same time.
Or you can drag the clothing file from the drawing window to the 3D window to open.
When you open it, you can set the loading type and the moving value.
Then, when you click select, the clothing file will automatically appear in the 3D window.
You can save the clothing file from the 3D window.
Click Save.
When you select the clothing file, click Save.
You can go to the 3D window of the 3D window and choose your 3D model.
Click Save.
When you click Save, the clothing file will be automatically saved and the moving value will appear.
Click Here to see it.
You can see that the clothing file has been saved.
If you need to delete the virtual model, you can select the virtual model and press the Delete button to delete it.
Click on the corresponding option on the main menu to save the virtual model file.
Select the appropriate path and enter the name and press the Save button.
Click on the corresponding option on the main menu to import the OBJ file.
After selecting the OBJ file to be imported, press the Open button.
In the pop-up menu, you can choose to open it directly or add it to the workspace.
You can choose to import the OBJ file to a virtual model.
You can adjust the import ratio, axis softening, and movement value.
You can choose to align the bottom of the object to the ground.
After pressing OK, the OBJ file will be imported to the virtual model.
In the item type, you can choose to import this OBJ file as a costume.
To select this image, you can remove the 2D version from the UV image.
Select the appropriate unit and click OK.
In the 3D window, you can see that the OBJ file has been imported as a costume.
After opening the simulation, the costume will be worn on the virtual model.
In addition, you can also import the OBJ file as a copy.
In the item type, you can choose to import it as a copy, then select the appropriate unit and click OK.
After importing the OBJ file, you can copy it to the costume by using the water-water tool.
When the water-water tool is in the right position, you can paste the object on the costume.
After opening the simulation, the weight of the object will affect the simulation effect.
You can export the object in the work area to the OBJ file by clicking the image option in the menu.
Select the path and then click the save button.
In the export menu, you can select which objects to export and the type of objects to export.
The bottom left is the selection of image about the UV image and the internal images.
The bottom right is the selection of the proportion of the rotation of the axis and the animation of the axis.
After the selection of the orientation of the axis, simply click theselft button to export.
In the export menu, you can see the selection of the assimilation of the movement of the steering wheel.
Click on the image in the main menu to import the FBX file.
Select the FBX file to be imported and click on the Open button.
Here you can choose the content to be imported.
You can choose to automatically add the function of arranging points.
You can set the proportion and unit of import according to your needs.
If there is a costume file in the work area, click on this image to move the costume to the action time.
After import, you can move the costume to the action time.
Click on the corresponding option in the main menu to import the FBX file.
Select the import path and enter the name and click on the save button.
In the export menu, you can set the type of the export object.
Here is the setting of the export animation.
Below is the setting of the proportion of the export file and unit.
The lowest is the export file and the type of text text, and click on the confirmation button to export.
By clicking the option in the corresponding main menu, you can import the elembic file.
Select the file to be imported and press the open button.
In the pop-up menu, you can set options such as FPS, ratio and unit.
If there is a costume file in the work area, click this to move the costume to the action time.
After import, you can move the costume and the virtual model together to simulate and record animation.
Click the corresponding option in the main menu to import the elembic file.
Select the file to be imported and press the open button.
Here you can adjust the type of export object and whether to use uniform UV settings.
You can select whether to export the virtual model together.
You can also set the FPS value of the export.
Here you can set theキー比例 and unit.
You can also set theキー比例和单位.
After completion, click the confirm button to export.
You can also set the GPA.
Here you can set the GPA.
After completion, click the confirm button to export.
You can also set the GPA.